IVAN CZAR

Software Engineering Graduate

ivanczar2013@gmail.comlinkedin.com/in/ivanczar/ivanczar.codes



CAREER SUMMARY:

I am a full-time Software Engineering student with experience working in **Scrum** teams, building mobile apps in **React Native**, using component libraries such as NativeBase, and connecting it to a **NoSQL** database such as Firebase. I have used **PHP** and **Java** in different projects to interact with **SQL** databases.

My goal is to write software that increases people's quality of life and to learn from those around me.

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Ben and Jerrys

Shift Leader - Catering Lead | Feb 2020 - Aug 2022

- Trained and lead a team of 13 scoopers, ensuring that all tasks were followed to a high standard.
- As catering lead, I was in charge of promoting, organizing, and executing the shop's catering service.
- Handled in-store complaints from customers, ordered stock from suppliers, and made sure that Food Health & Safety reports were up to date.

RELEVANT PROJECTS:

SportsHub

Mobile Development | March 2022 - June 2022

- Built a mobile app in React Native that allows athletes to host and join sporting events. It
 includes features such as a public chat, an editable profile, and the ability for users to join
 teams.
- Followed the Agile Scrum framework, acting as scrum master in a team of five.

Marketplace Webscraper

Web Development | August 2022

 Built a bot in Python and Selenium that scrapes the Neighbourly marketplace for items listed for free, or that satisfy a set of keywords and sends me a notification via the Twilio API.

Personal Web Portfolio

Web Development | July 2022

• Created a responsive personal portfolio website using React and the Styled Components library to showcase my work and ultimately increase my online presence.

EDUCATION:

2020 - 2023 | Auckland University of Technology

Bachelor of Engineering (Honours) - Software Engineering | GPA: 7.125 (First Class Honours)

SKILLS:

- Agile (Scrum)
- Autodidact
- Clear verbal and written communication
- Dedicated and hard working
- Critical thinking skills